Guide to the Clarence W. Rowley Papers Relating to Buffalo Bill and John L. Sullivan
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Business Papers, 1905-1924; Series IV; 0.21; (1 box)
  - HIGH JINKS GOLD MINING COMPANY
    - Notes, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 161)
  - JOHN L. SULLIVAN MOTION PICTURE COMPANY
    - Description of company, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 162)
  - MONTEZUMA MINING COMPANY
    - Shareholder resolutions, 1906 (Box 6, Folder 163)
    - Stock certificates, 1905-1906 (Box 6, Folder 164-165)
  - MONTEZUMA SILVER MINES CORPORATION
    - Stock certificates, 1919 Jul 22 (Box 6, Folder 166)
    - Stockholder report, 1924 Jul 17 (Box 6, Folder 167)
- Subject Files, 1893-1918; Series V; 0.21; (1 box)
  Series V, Subject Files is organized into two subseries: Buffalo Bill and John L. Sullivan. Material in each subseries has been arranged by type of material.
  - BUFFALO BILL
    - Biographical sketch, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 168)
    - Clippings, 1897-1917, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 169-170)
    - The Indian. Buffalo Bill's Art Studies with Portraits of Himself, [aft. 1910]
  - JOHN L. SULLIVAN
    - Affadavit of debt for estate of JLS, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 171)
    - "A Recitation or Toast to Woman", typescript poem, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 172)
    - Clippings, 1916-1918, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 173-174)
    - Material found in pants pocket at time of death (Box 6, Folder 175)
    - Notes, 1917, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 176)
    - The Outlook 3, no. 9 (October 1915), 1915 Oct 27 (Box 6, Folder 177)
      Contains article on JLS.
    - Postcard, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 178)
    - Printed ephemera, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 179)
    - Speeches: manuscript and typescript (Box 6, Folder 180-181)
    - Trading card, [1893?] (Box 6, Folder 182)
- Other Papers, 1911-1917; Series VI; 0.21; (1 box)
  Series VI, Other Papers, is arranged alphabetically by type or title of material.
  - Autograph: Henry Ward Beecher, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 183)
  - Cripple Creek Consolidated Mining and Milling Company: printed prospectus (Box 6, Folder 184)
  - Fielding, F. E., "Report on the Campo Bonito and Southern Belle Mining and Milling Company, Pinal County, Arizona": typescript, 1911 Aug 18 (Box 6, Folder 185)
  - Notes, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 186)
  - "Resolution adopted at Fanueil Hall, Boston": typescript announcement, 1917 Mar 14 (Box 6, Folder 187)
- Oversize, 1.58; (1 box)
  - Hanff, Joseph H. to John L. Sullivan (in Correspondence), 1917 Jul 13 (Box 7, Folder 188)
  - Cripple Creek Consolidated Mining and Milling Company (in Photographs) (Box 7, Folder 189-193)
  - Clarence Rowley. Portrait by Elmer Chickering. On horse (in Photographs), n.d. (Box 7, Folder 194)
  - Clarence Rowley. Portrait by Elmer Chickering. Seated (in Photographs), 1905 (Box 7, Folder 195)
  - Buffalo Bill. TE Ranch (in Photographs), n.d. (Box 7, Folder 196-200)
  - Buffalo Bill's Wild West and Pawnee Bill's Great Far East show. Performers (in Photographs) (Box 7, Folder 201)
  - John L. Sullivan. Portrait by J. M. Mora (in Photographs), 1882 (Box 7, Folder 202)
  - John L. Sullivan. Siegel Studio portraits (in Photographs), 1918, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 203-205)
  - The Indian. Buffalo Bill's Art Studies with Portraits of Himself (in Subject Files), [aft. 1910] (Box 7, Folder 206)